https://www.searchenginegenie.com/privacy-policy.htm

MENU
SEO
Search Engine Optimization Search Engine Manipulation Articles SEO For Auto Transporters Search Engine Marketing SEO Consulting SEO Problems SEO Plans SEO Plans Comparision SEO Services US SEO Forum SEO Comics SEO Faq SEO Resellers Subscribe SEO Newsletter Search Engine Expert Directory SEO Knowledge Base
Blogs
SEO Blog SEO News SEO Copywriting Blog Google Product Search Blog Pay Per Click Blog Programming Blog Link Building Blog Web Design Blog Search Engine Genie Blog
100 Web Tools
Google Tools Widget Yahoo Tools MSN Tools Text Tools Comparison Tools Link Popularity Tools Search Engines Tools Site Tools Keyword Tools Javascript Tools Miscellaneous Tools
Services
Web Design Link Building Internet Marketing Ecommerce Implementation Pay Per Click Services Google Product Search Shopping Feeds Optimization Shopping Cart Customization Product Development Programming Services Online Forms & Database Integration PHP Programming Services Programming Services Java,J2EE .Net Application Development Programmming Services Business process outsourcing Offshore Outsourcing
Link Building
Link Popularity Strategies Of Link Building Link Building Services Link Building Costs Advanced Link Building Strategies Link Building Request Quote
Web Design
Web Designing services Web Design Portfolio Dynamic Websites Web Design Marketing Simple E-Commerce Website Complex E-Commerce Search Engine Friendly Site
Articles
SEO Articles Search Engine Optimization Articles Google Articles Yahoo Articles Pay Per Click Articles Miscelleneous Articles
Contact Us
Contact Us About Us Client Testimonials Why us Search Engine Genie Company Support Our Guarantee Our Team Our Experience Our Clients Case Studies Our Celebrations Leave Feedback Career Opportunity
SEO Home
Privacy Policy
Search Engine Privacy Policy
Search Engine Genie has created
this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our commitment to the
privacy and protection of your information. As part of the normal
operation of services, we collect and, in some instances, disclose
information about you. To better protect your privacy, we provide
this notice explaining our information practices and the choices
you can make about the way your information is collected and used.
1. Information Collected During Your Use of the Search Engine Genie Service
In order to register, users are required to give
us contact information (e.g., your name and email address), unique
identifiers (e.g., your password), and demographic information (e.g.,
your zip code). Certain information, such as passwords and email
addresses, is collected in order to verify your identity and for
use in our records.
If you decide to purchase any Search Engine
Genie Solutions, Search Engine Genie will
need to collect certain financial information, such as your credit
card number, credit card expiration date, and billing address ("Financial
Information"). Financial Information that is collected is used
to check your qualifications for registration, to bill you for products
and services, and for other purposes. Search Engine Genie does not
share Financial Information with outside parties except to the extent
necessary to provide you with Search Engine Genie Solutions.
2. Our Use of Your Information
We use customer contact information from the registration
form to send you information about Search
Engine Genie and promotional material from
some of our partners. Your contact information is also used to contact
you when necessary. We may use your IP address to help protect our
partners and us from fraud.
We may use demographic and profile data to tailor
your experience on our service, showing you content that we think
you might be interested in, and displaying the content according
to your preferences.
3. Our Disclosure of Your
Information
We never use or share the personally identifiable
information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones
described in this Privacy Policy and our Member Agreement without
also providing you an opportunity to opt out or otherwise prohibit
such unrelated uses. We may also offer you the option to attract
visitors to your site through participation in search engines, comparative
shopping services, or similar distribution opportunities.
Search Engine
Genie will never willfully sell, lease, or
rent any of your or your business' personally identifiable information
to any third party without first receiving your permission.
Search Engine
Genie offers features and services on our site
where we will need to provide some of the information publicly available
on your Member Site to third-party search engines offering search
services. Should you choose to use any of these features and services,
we may do the following with such information: distribute member
product and service information and information about your store,
your products and services, your web site address (URL), your contact
information, and other information, to such search engines and various
other comparative shopping and search services; and create a database
of publicly available information about you or your business to
its search partners with the express purpose of driving Internet
user traffic to Member Sites, provided that such information is
useful to the end users of the Member Sites. Publicly available
information means information available to the public on your web
site, and may include the following: information about the products
or services you offer through the Member Site, your operating hours,
your business address, your URL, your business contact information,
and other such information. In no event, however, will we disclose
any of your Financial Information.
Search Engine
Genie cannot ensure that all of your personally
identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not described
in this Privacy Policy. For instance, we may be required to disclose
personally identifiable information to the government or by court
order under certain circumstances, or other situations that may
require such disclosure. In addition, you authorize us to disclose
any information about you to law enforcement or other government
officials as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate.
This site contains links to other sites. Search Engine Genie is not responsible for
the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.
4. Security
In order to maximize the protection of your information, Search Engine Genie Service uses state-of-the-art technology to protect your data from
use, misuse, or alteration by unauthorized third parties. Currently,
we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol to protect your data
and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information,
including your credit card number, name, and address, as it is transmitted
over the Internet. Of course, no data transmission over the Internet
can be guaranteed to be one hundred percent secure, and Search
Engine Genie does not warrant that your information
will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data on or through
the use of the Search Engine Genie Service is at your own risk.
5. General
This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject
to the terms of the Search Engine
Genie Member Agreement.
6. Cookie Usage and EU cookie concent policy:
Search Engine Genie may sometimes use cookies to personalize your experience. Cookies are used to recognize you through your web browser. You have the right to accept or reject a cookie. This option is available in all browsers.
Search engine genie serves third party advertisements like Google adsense to serve ads. Google adsense uses cookies to serve best and relevant ads to you. Google uses DART cookie which will serve personalized ads. Google also serves ads based on your interests and searches online by using a cookie.
Browsers can be set to accept or reject cookies or notify you when a cookie is being sent. Privacy software can be used to override web beacons. Taking either of these actions should not cause a problem with our site.
European union cookie consent policy:
Search Engine Genie complies with EU cookie consent policy.
Cancellation and refund policy
Click Here to Make Payment
Disclaimer SEG
For more information on Search Engine Genie’s
services, contact us at webpromotions@gmail.com
SEO
Search engine optimization
SEO For Auto Transporters
Offshore outsourcing
Google Products(froogle feeds)
Articles
Articles
SEO Articles
Search
engine optimization Articles
Google
Articles
Yahoo
Programming blog sitemap
Search Engine Optimization SEO Company | Privacy Policy | Term of Service | Copyright
Search Engine Genie is an Ethical Search Engine Optimization Company Specializing in Search Engine Marketing, Search Engine Promotion and Search Engine Ranking Services.
